const contest_1_1 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "A uniform meter stick carries a $20 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $15 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark and a $30 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $60 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark.",
        "Question": "At which mark must the meter stick be placed on a knife edge in order to be in equilibrium?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$42 \\mathrm{~cm}$\n$$\nx=\\left(m_{1} l_{1}+m_{2} l_{2}\\right) /\\left(m_{1}+m_{2}\\right)=(20 \\mathrm{~g} \\times 15 \\mathrm{~cm}+30 \\mathrm{~g} \\times 60 \\mathrm{~cm}) /(20 \\mathrm{~g}+30 \\mathrm{~g})=42 \\mathrm{~cm}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "A uniform meter stick carries a $20 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $15 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark and a $30 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $60 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark.",
        "Question": "If the $20 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass were moved to the $10 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark while keeping the $30 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $60 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark, at which mark must the knife edge be located?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$40 \\mathrm{~cm}$\n$$\nx=\\left(m_{1} l_{1}+m_{2} l_{2}\\right) /\\left(m_{1}+m_{2}\\right)=(20 \\mathrm{~g} \\times 10 \\mathrm{~cm}+30 \\mathrm{~g} \\times 60 \\mathrm{~cm}) /(20 \\mathrm{~g}+30 \\mathrm{~g})=40 \\mathrm{~cm}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "A uniform meter stick carries a $20 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $15 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark and a $30 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $60 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark.",
        "Question": "If instead the $30 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass were moved to the $75 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark while keeping the $20 \\mathrm{~g}$ mass at the $15 \\mathrm{~cm}$ mark, at which mark must the knife edge now be located?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$51 \\mathrm{~cm}$\n$$\nx=\\left(m_{1} l_{1}+m_{2} l_{2}\\right) /\\left(m_{1}+m_{2}\\right)=(20 \\mathrm{~g} \\times 15 \\mathrm{~cm}+30 \\mathrm{~g} \\times 75 \\mathrm{~cm}) /(20 \\mathrm{~g}+30 \\mathrm{~g})=51 \\mathrm{~cm}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Determine the angle of refraction when light falls at an angle of incidence of $30^{\\circ}$ from air onto glass of refractive index 1.53 .",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$19^{\\circ}$\n$$\n\\theta_{r}=\\left(\\sin \\theta_{i}\\right) / n=\\left[\\left(\\sin 30^{\\circ}\\right) / 1.53\\right]=19^{\\circ}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Light is incident from air into glass of refractive index 1.62 at an angle of incidence of $30^{\\circ}$. Find the angle of refraction.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$18^{\\circ}$\n$$\n\\theta_{r}=\\left(\\sin \\theta_{i}\\right) / n=\\left[\\left(\\sin 30^{\\circ}\\right) / 1.62\\right]=18^{\\circ}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Determine the angle of refraction when light falls at an angle of incidence of $30^{\\circ}$ from air onto diamond. The refractive index of diamond at the light wavelength is 2.45.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$12^{\\circ}$\n$$\n\\theta_{r}=\\left(\\sin \\theta_{i}\\right) / n=\\left[\\left(\\sin 30^{\\circ}\\right) / 2.45\\right]=12^{\\circ}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Which of the elements, hydrogen and lithium, has the higher first ionisation energy?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Hydrogen. (Hydrogen $1312 \\mathrm{kJmol}^{-1}$; Lithium $520 \\mathrm{kJmol}^{-1}$ )",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Which of the two elements, sodium and magnesium has the higher enthalpy of atomisation?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Magnesium. (Mg $148 \\mathrm{kJmol}^{-1} ; \\quad \\mathrm{Na} \\quad 107 \\mathrm{kJmol}^{-1}$ )",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Which of the elements, oxygen and sulphur has the higher (negative) electron affinity?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Sulphur. $\\quad\\left(\\mathrm{S} \\quad-200 \\mathrm{kJmol}^{-1} ; 0 \\quad-141 \\mathrm{kJmol}^{-1}\\right.$ )",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Calculate the formula mass of the compound $\\mathrm{NaAl}(\\mathrm{OH})_{2} \\mathrm{CO}_{3}$.\n$\\mathrm{Al}=27.0 ; \\mathrm{Na}=23.0 ; \\mathrm{O}=16.0 ; \\mathrm{C}=12.0 ; \\mathrm{H}=1.00$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\operatorname{NaAl}(\\mathrm{OH})_{2} \\mathrm{CO}_{3}=\\quad 23.0+27.0+34.0+60.0=144$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Calculate the formula mass of the complex compound $\\mathrm{Fe}_{4}\\left[\\mathrm{Fe}(\\mathrm{CN})_{6}\\right]_{3}$.\nFe $=56.0 ; \\mathrm{N}=14.0 ; \\mathrm{C}=12.0$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\mathrm{Fe}_{4}\\left[\\mathrm{Fe}(\\mathrm{CN})_{6}\\right]_{3}=4 * 56.0+[56.0+6 * 26]^{* 3}$\n$$\n=224+3[56.0+156]=860\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Determine the molar mass of diazepam, also known as Valium whose formula is $\\mathrm{C}_{16} \\mathrm{H}_{13} \\mathrm{ClN}_{2} \\mathrm{O}$.\n$\\mathrm{Cl}=35.5 ; \\mathrm{O}=16.0 ; \\mathrm{N}=14.0 ; \\mathrm{C}=12.0 ; \\quad \\mathrm{H}=1.00$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\quad \\mathrm{C}_{16} \\mathrm{H}_{13} \\mathrm{ClN}_{2} \\mathrm{O}=(16 * 12.0)+13.0+35.5+28.0+16.0=284.5$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 13,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Evaluate the given limit",
        "Question": "$\\operatorname{Lim}_{h \\rightarrow 0} \\frac{(h-5)^{2}-25}{h}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "-10\n$\\left[\\left(h^{2}-10 h\\right) / h=h-10\\right.$, hence limit as $h$ tends to 0 is -10$]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 14,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Evaluate the given limit",
        "Question": "$\\operatorname{Lim}_{h \\rightarrow 0} \\frac{(2+h)^{2}-4}{h}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\left[\\left(4 h+h^{2}\\right) / h=4+h\\right.$, hence limit as $h$ tends to 0 is 4",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 15,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Evaluate the given limit",
        "Question": "$\\operatorname{Lim}_{h \\rightarrow 0} \\frac{(3-h)^{2}-9}{h}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$- 6$\n$\\left[\\left(h^{2}-6 h\\right) / h=-6+h\\right.$, hence limit as $h$ tends to 0 is -6$]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 16,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the area of a parallelogram if",
        "Question": "the area is represented by $x^{2}$, the base by $x+3$ and the altitude by $x-2$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "36 sq. units\n$\\left[x^{2}=(x+3)(x-2)=x^{2}+x-6, x-6=0, x=6\\right.$ hence area $\\left.x^{2}=6^{2}=36\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 17,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the area of a parallelogram if",
        "Question": "the area is represented by $x^{2}-10$, the base by $x$ and the altitude by $x-2$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "15 sq. units\n$\\left[x^{2}-10=x(x-2)=x^{2}-2 x, 2 x=10, x=5\\right.$, area $\\left.x^{2}-10=25-10=15\\right]$,",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 18,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the area of a parallelogram if",
        "Question": "the area is represented by $2 x^{2}-34$, the base by $x+3$ and the altitude by $x-3$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "16 sq. units\n$\\left[2 x^{2}-34=(x+3)(x-3)=x^{2}-9, x^{2}=34-9=25, x=5\\right.$,\narea $\\left.=2 x^{2}-34=2(25)-34=50-34=16\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 19,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Permanent tissues in plants may be classified on the basis of origin or function. Mention one permeant tissue on the basis of function.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "a) Photosynthetic or assimilatory tissue.\nb) Food storing tissue.\nc) Conducting or vascular tissue.\nd) Secretory tissue\ne) Mechanical tissue\nf) Protective tissue",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 20,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Which molecules play the key role in the transfer of genetic information during protein synthesis?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "RNA molecules (DNA has all the information which is confined to the nucleus, it is only transferred with the help of RNA during protein synthesis.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 21,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Which of the RNA molecules convert information stored in the nucleic acid to protein?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "tRNA",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 22,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Which RNA molecule acts as an interface between nucleic acid language and protein language?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "tRNA",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    }
]


export default contest_1_1